oki.com 2019-07-09

# Privacy Policy | OKI Global

## OKI Electric Industry Co., Ltd. and OKI Group Privacy Policy

The corporate philosophy of OKI Electric Industry Co., Ltd. and OKI Group (hereinafter, "OKI Group") is to "provide products that contribute to the development of an information society, while upholding an 'enterprising spirit' and to realize a comfortable and affluent life for the people of the world." In recognition of its duty to contribute to an information-driven society, OKI Group delivers "peace of mind" to its customers via its telecommunications products and services. Based on this, the OKI Group implements the following measures to protect personal information it handles.

  1. Each company in the OKI Group will provide information about the purpose and scope of use of any personal information received by the company in response to a customer inquiry. It will put in place measures to ensure that the purpose and scope of use of this information are not exceeded.
  2. The OKI Group will not disclose stored personal information to a Third Party unless otherwise agreed beforehand, or if it is required by law.
  3. The OKI Group shall implement security measures and remedies to prevent stored personal information from being leaked, lost or compromised.
  4. The OKI Group shall strictly abide by all applicable laws, regulations, guidelines and standards set by the government regarding the storage of personal information.
  5. The OKI Group shall promote the proper handling of personal information, in addition to establishing a personal information manager for each department that handles personal information. Moreover, it will provide training and education to anyone engaged in activities related to the handling of personal information.
  6. The OKI Group will ensure that it responds within a reasonable period of time to any complaints or inquiries or requests for verification, revision or deletion of personal information that it receives from its customer.
  7. The OKI Group will continually work to improve its management system to protect personal information.

OKI Electric Industry Co., Ltd.  
Representative Director and President, Shinya Kamagami

## Inquiries about our policies:

Our customer services desk is happy to respond to any views on the above contents or questions regarding the protection of personal information. 

## Regarding the Personal Information Manager

Personal Information Manager  
Contact: Same as for inquiries on the protection of personal information 

## Purpose of the use of personal information

OKI Electric Co. Ltd. (hereinafter, "Company") announces that personal information is used follows, in accordance with the Personal Information Protection Act, Articles 18 and 27 in Japan.

  1. To sell personal information products and services related to customers 
    * To provide maintenance support
    * To provide information to the customer
    * To fulfill a contract
    * To deliver products and services
    * To introduce new products at seminars and exhibitions, etc.
    * To provide information related to the Company's activities
    * To respond to various inquiries
  2. Personal Information in relation to suppliers. 
    * To contact and negotiate with suppliers
    * To fulfill a contract
    * To pay invoices and charges
  3. Personal information regarding shareholders. 
    * To exercise rights and fulfill obligations in accordance with the Commercial Code
    * To provide benefits on behalf of the Company
    * To implement measures to build relationships between the Company and its shareholders
    * To manage shareholder affairs, such as the production of shareholder data based on the prescribed standards, in accordance with relevant laws
  4. Personal information regarding those who wish to join the Company. 
    * To contact or provide employment/recruitment information to those who have an interest in working at the Company or who have applied for a job at the Company
    * To select employees for recruitment
  5. Personal information related to inquiries. 
    * To respond to inquiries and provide information
  6. Personal information entrusted by clients. 
    * To fulfill contractual arrangements with clients

Furthermore, if there is separate notification of the purpose of use, this purpose of use shall apply.

Items 1 - 5 above are disclosed personal information. Item 6 is undisclosed personal information.

Moreover, the personal information collected by the Company includes information provided directly to the Company by the customer, information pertaining to the use of services and information obtained from a Third Party.

## Period of Storage of Personal Information

The Company may store personal information for amount of time required to perform the purpose of use of this information.

## Provision of Personal Information to a Third Party

The Company will not provide personal information to a Third Party except in the following cases.

  * If the individual has given consent
  * If a law requires disclosure
  * For the protection of life or property, where it is difficult to obtain consent from the individual

## Entrustment of Personal Information

Personal information may be entrusted to the extent necessary for achieving the purpose of use.

## Transfer of Personal Information to a Third Country

The Company is developing its business outside Japan. Personal information obtained outside Japan may be transferred to Japan for processing and storage. In this case, the Company will follow applicable laws and implement the necessary, appropriate measures for the protection of personal information.

## Concerning Personal Information of Customers under 16

A guardian's consent is required for any personal information provided to the Company by customers under 16 years old.

## Provision of Personal Information

The provision of personal information is in principle voluntary. It may be required depending on the type of service. We will inform customers if the information is required. Please be aware that there are some services that cannot be provided without the submission of personal information.

## Regarding procedures in response to "Disclosure requests"

The Company will respond within a reasonable period of time, within the scope required for the achievement of the purpose of use of the information, if there is an inquiry or request for correction, addition or deletion of details regarding personal information from a customer or his/her proxy.  
Please make any requests regarding the handling of customers' personal information via the contact point indicated at the time of registration.  
Furthermore, if you are unclear about who to contact, please make your inquiry via the customer services desk for the protection of personal information. We will respond to inquiries after checking the details concerned. 

1-7-12 Toranomon, Minato, Tokyo (Toranomon First Garden), 105-8460, Japan  
OKI Electric Industry Co., Ltd. Customer services desk for the protection of personal information 

## Complaints related to Personal Information and Customer Services

Please contact the customer services desk for the protection of personal information, if you have any complaints or concerns regarding personal information. 

1-7-12 Toranomon, Minato, Tokyo (Toranomon First Garden), 105-8460, Japan  
OKI Electric Industry Co., Ltd. Customer services desk for the protection of personal information 

In addition, if you are outside Japan and wish to raise a complaint, you can file a complaint with the Data Protection Supervisory Authority in your country.

## About the OKI Website

The Company will strictly adhere to the personal information policy outlined above in the handling of any personal information provided via an OKI Website inquiry form or an email.  
Furthermore, the Company will bear no responsibility for the protection of customers' personal information in relation to other websites linked to the OKI website.

### Use of Cookies

A cookie is a small piece of data sent by a web server to a customer's browser that is stored as a file on the customer's hard disk. The computer being used can be identified by the use of a cookie, but the user cannot be identified.

The Company may use cookies on the OKI website to provide better services customized for each customer's use. The customer can deactivate cookies by going to his/her browser settings. Certain services may become unavailable in that case.

## Privacy Mark

In Japan, OKI Electric has been awarded Privacy Mark accreditation by JIPDEC.

The PrivacyMark recognizes operators that meet the Japanese industrial standard requirements for the secure handling of personal information based on the "Personal information protection management system - Requirements (JIS Q 15001).

Top of this page
